Guide to the Office of Marketing and Communication records ARCH115
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
- Acc. I. Unknown (People Photographs), 14.21 Linear Feet (35 containers)
  - L-Log (Box L-Log)
    LeBlanc, Claudette
    Ledbetter, James
    Lee
    Lee, Jim
    Lee, John
    Lee, John with Hillyer students
    Lehman
    Leiterman-Stock, Peggy
    Lenfest, Rodney
    Lennon, Susan
    Leo the Dog
    Leonhardt, Gustav
    Leonhardt, Harry
    Leonhardt, Mrs. Harry
    Lerak, Alexander
    Leser, Paul
    Lessing, Christine
    LeSure, James
    Lev, Danielle
    Levesque, Lauri
    Levine, Caryl with Elaine Cooper
    Levine, Jessica
    Levy, Joanna
    Lewis, Brenda
    Lewis, Brian
    Lewis, gary
    Lewis, Richard
    Lewis, Thomas Skipworth
    Li, Tieh-tseng
    Liakas, Nicholas
    Libassi, F. Peter
    Libassi, Peter
    Libby, Haddon
    Library Staff/Library of Congress Celebration softball game, 2000
    Library Staff/Ron Epps going away party
    Lichtenstein, Benjamyn Bergman
    Lidell Townsell and MTF
    Lieberman, Joseph
    Lievano, Rod
    Lind, Abraham
    Lindsay, Delois and Rob Fried and Larry Williams
    Lion's Gate Trio
    Lipmonger
    Little Anthony and the Imperials
    Little Sister
    LoBrutto, Rhonda Dublain
    Loessin, Bruce
    Logan, Robert
  - Lol-Ma (Box Lol-Ma)
    Lomaglio, Peter
    Long, Doonald
    Long, Grayce
    Lopez, Luciano (Bob)
    Los Gusanos
    Lostoco, Mr. and Mrs.
    Lott, John
    Loud, Frederick
    Love, Thomas
    Lowenstein, Amy
    Loy, Helen
    Lucarelli, Humbert
    Lucas, Sue
    Luebke, Barbara
    Lugli, Richard
    Lulabox
    Lurie, Bernard
    Lurtsema, Robert J.
    Lussier, Michele with Nancy Shula and Theresa Fiamengo
    Luxenburg, Virginia
    Lyle, Kami
    Lyman, Mrs. Henry
    Lynch, Brendan
    Ma'Oz, Moshe
    Macchia, Salvatore
    MacCluggage, Reid
    Macco, Allison
    Macio
    Mack, Gerald
    Mack, John
    MacNeil, with Moshe Paranov and Irene Kahn
    MacNeill, Cornell
    Maguder, Theodore Jr.
    Mahan, Thomas W. Jr.
    Mailer, Norman
    Mali, Paul
    Mancini, Charles
    Mandell, Judyt and Thomas Halstead and Percy Longstaff
    Mankiewicz, frank
    Manley, Michael
    Mann, Nicholas
    Manternach, Bruce
    Mapes, James
    Mapes, Jim
    Margarones, john
    Marijosius, Vytautas
    Markham, Walter
    Markson, Stephen
    Marot-Sir, Edward
    Marsalis, Wynton
    Marshall, John
    Martin, Gail
    Martin, John G.
    Martin, Linda
    Martin, Ralph
    Martin, Richard S.
    Marvin, keith
    Marx, richard
    Maseda, Maria
    Massa, Andy
    Masselos, William
    Massey, Steve
    Materialissue
    Mathews, James
    Matiwala, Luuai
    Matthias, Virginia
    Mattran, Donald A.
    Mauer, Barbara
    Maxym, Steven
    May, Rollo
    Maycock, Daniel
    Mayer, Henrik
    Mayer, Howard
    Maynard, Frederick C., Jr.
  - Mc-Mo (Box Mc-Mo)
    McBride, Daniel
    McBride, John
    McCarthy, Rosemary
    McClean, Jackie
    McClean, Jackie/with students
    McClintock, Bruce
    McCloud, Gavin and Beverly Sills
    McCormick, Joseph
    McCormick, Kathy
    McCullough, Gordon
    McCullough, Gordon with Senator Thomas Dodd
    McDaniel, Elizabeth
    McDiers, Ann with Paul Klen and Peter Mansfield
    McDonough, Edward
    McDuffie, Thomas
    McGann, Joe
    McGavern, John
    McGivney, Raymond
    McGlade, Keith
    McGuire, John
    McKee, Clyde
    McKinley, Patricia See also HCW photos
    McLean, Peter
    McNeil, George
    McNeill, George
    McNeill, William
    Means, Blanchard
    Meinfield, Bruce
    Meinke, Kenneth
    Mellon, Biff in bookstore
    Mende, rose
    Menuhin
    Menuhin, Yehudi see also two scrapbooks of Menuhin's visit to Hartt
    Merck, Edwin
    Middendorf, J. William II
    Mihalek, Paul
    Milek, Theodore
    Miles, Wilford
    Miller, Arthur
    Miller, Chris
    Miller, Edward
    Miller, Elaine
    Miller, Henry with Phlip Landrey and John Riccio
    Miller, Jonathan
    Miller, Patrick
    Miller, Regina
    Milliken, Jo
    Millner, Brenda
    Mills, Dick
    Miner, Jan
    Minter, Jeff
    Missirian, Agnes
    Mitchell, James
    Mitchell, Jim
    Mixashawn
    Modigliani, Franco
    Moffett, Kenworth
    Moffett, Toby
    Moller, Marino, Dians
    Mooney, Robert
    Moore, Douglas
    Moore, Richard
    Moran, Martin with Pres. Trachtenberg, Jesse Jackson and Thirman Milner
    Morales, Hilda
    Moreland, Tamara
    Morgan (woman)
    Morgan, john
    Morgan, Sandra
    Morrison
    Morrison, Malcolm
    Morrison, Toni
    Morrison, tony
    Morrison, Watson
    Mortensen, William
    Moseley, Edwain
    Moseley, Stephen
    Mothers of Invention and Frank Zappa
    Motiwalla, Luuai
  - Mul-O (Box Mul-O)
    Mu330
    Mulcahy, Gene
    Mulling, Seymour
    Murdock, James
    Murmurs
    Murphy, Franklin
    Murphy, Jean
    Murphy, John Davis and Robert h. Murphey/Wiremold
    Murray, david
    Murray, Robert
    Murtha, Roger
    Music education faculty
    Mustard Plug
    Myles, Jack
    Mystery Machine
    Nader, Ralph
    Nader, Ralph, former University professor
    Nagurney, Ladimer
    Nagy, Elemer
    Najoom, Dennis
    Narduzzi, James
    Nason, Rachel
    Neal, Tom
    Neaman, Yfrah
    Near, Holly
    Neil, Cornel
    Neisloss, Russ
    Nemetz, Miriam
    Newell, Robert
    Newman, Edwin
    Newman, John
    Newman, Jon
    Newmann, Otto and Herman La Fontaine, Anne M. Crawford and Betty Sternberg
    Nichols, Edward
    Nickel, Karl
    Nickrenz, Scott
    Nogaard, corine
    Nolan, William
    Nonchalant
    Norr, Queen see Walt's Wall oversize box
    Northern Pikes, The
    Norton, Jane
    Nowak, Lionel
    Nussbaum, Irwin
    O'Brien, Robert
    O'Connell, Maurice
    O'Neill, Governor
    O'Neill, Rose
    O'Neill, Thomas "Tip"
    O'Neill, Tip
    O'Neill, William
    Governor with Trachtenberg
    O'Reilly, Christopher
    O'Sullivan, Father John J.
    Ogilvie, John
    Olitski, Jules
    Olsen, Richard
    Orfanolla, Perry
    Orhan, Volkau
    Orlon, Volkan
    Osekne, Bess A. assistant reference librarian
    Otis, Cynthia
    Ouerstrom, Gunnar
  - P-Press (Box P-Press)
    Pachla, Jill
    Paltro, Gwyneth
    Pandova, Mark in regents' Park apartment
    Panik, Michael
    Papazian, Arthur
    Paranous and others
    Paranov
    Paranov, Elizabeth
    Paranov, Elizabeth Warner, see also Elizabeth Warner
    Paranov, Moshe
    Paranov, Moshe, see also Paranov collection
    Parente, Ralph
    Paretti, Mark
    Park, Mike
    Park, Rosemary, President of Connecticut College
    Parker, Alice
    Parker, Daniel
    Parker, Karen and David Wasser
    Parker, Raymond
    Parker, the Rev. F. D.
    Parlardy, Theresa
    Patota, Joan
    Patrick, Erline
    Patterson, Jeremiah
    Patti, Charles
    Payne, Maggie
    Peart, Jacqueline
    Peck, Dexter
    Peking Youth Art Theater
    Pelikan, Jaroslav
    Pelletier, Marcia
    Pelletieri, Louis
    Pelli, Cesar
    Pengel, Joachim
    Pepyne, Edward
    Perkins, Francis
    Perle, George
    Perry, Pamela
    Peskin, Jennifer
    Peters, Ellen Ash
    Peters, James
    Peters, Louis
    Peters, Mayor Mike
    Petersen, Erin and Sherlene Blackwood/Volunteers for Excellence, 1990
    Peterson, Glade
    Peterson, Peter
    Peterson, Roger Torrey
    Phelan, Jack
    Phelan, Maureen
    Piccolo, Lynn Strow
    Piccora, Lynn Strow
    Pierce, Ann
    Pilagin, Loretta
    Pilonis, Ray
    Pinsky favorite poem project
    Pious, Stephanie Kass
    Platt, George
    Pleuther, Willard A.
    Poe, Pascal
    Polardy, Theresa
    Polk, Cassie
    Pollack, Eileen
    Polsky, Lisa
    Pomfret, Bonnie
    Pond, Sam
    Popdi, Alberat
    Pope, Sharon
    Poravski, Judy and Christopher Bailey
    Poriett, Jerome
    Post, Charles
    Post, Mildred
    Potter, Holly
    Poussaint, Alan F.
    Pratt, Waldo Selden
    Preble, Lenore
    Prentice, Mrs. T. Merrill
    Prentice, Theodora
    Prescott, Jean/Reference Librarian
    Pressley, Beatrice Orr
  - Pri-Qui; Ra-Ri (Box Pri-Qui; Ra-Ri)
    Prichard, William
    Prioleau, Marguerite
    Pritting, Randi Ashton with John McGavern
    Prud'homme, Hector
    Prud'homme, Hector with Trachtenberg, Ellsworth, Prentice
    Prusank, Diane
    Pryor, Millard
    Puccino, James
    Puskarz, Anna
    Putnam, Albert
    Putnam, Rosalind
    Putsche, Thomas
    Pye, A. Kenneth
    Quinn, Andrew
    Quintin, Muriel
    Radiators, The
    Ragosta family
    Rahn, Richard
    Rai, Doreen
    Ramsey, Gordon Clark
    Ranche, Anthony
    Rand, Paul
    Randall, Donna
    Ransom, Norman and Arthur Peterson
    Raphael Trio
    Rauche, Anthony
    Rave-Ups, The
    Ravosa, Carmino
    Raymond, Christopher
    Rebmann, Andrew
    Redfield, Mason
    Redfield, Richard
    Reeves, Nat
    Regan, Timothy
    Regents/individuals/portraits on DVD
    Regnier, J. Ronald
    Regnier, J. Ronald and Haskell
    Reich, Steve
    Reilly, Charles Nelson
    Reinhardt, Uwe
    Reischl, Bridget-Michaele
    Rell, Jody. See Walt's Wall oversize box
    Repass, Robert, "Bob" "Spike"
    Resnick, Harvey
    Resnick, Judy
    Resta, Francis with Eugene Cipriano, Louis Pontecorvo, Harvey Goldstein, Gerald Marks, Maurice Haag, and Harold Portner
    Rhone, Jeffrey
    Ribicoff, Abraham
    Ribicoff, Abraham with Bernard Goodman and A.M. Woodruff
    Ribicoff, Belle
    Rice, Marjory
    Rich, Anne
    Rich, L. Ashley
    Richardson, Minnie-Rose
    Richmond, Trudi with Miki Rawls and Kathleen King "Native Americans"
    Riggs, Steve
    Rigialado, Antonio
    Ringgold, Faith
    Ritvo, Cynthia
  - Ro-Sav (Box Ro-Sav)
    Robbins, William
    Roberti, Vincent
    Roberto, Francesca
    Roberts, Henry
    Roberts, Margaret
    Robertson, Robbie
    Robinson, Leo
    Rockas, Leo
    Roderick, John
    Rodnofsky, Kenneth
    Roessner, Barbara with Worth Loomis
    Roettger, Peggy
    Rogers, Kenny
    Rohmann, Henrik
    Romero, Gustavo
    Rollins, Sonny
    Ronstrom, Robert
    Roosa, Vernon
    Root, Steve
    Rose, John
    Rose, Leonard
    Rosenbaum, Jonathan
    Rosenberg, Steven
    Rosenblatt, Howard
    Rosenthal, Steven
    Ross, Charles
    Ross, David
    Ross, Lisa
    Rostapovich
    Rostropovich, Msistlav
    Roth, Phillip
    Roth, Richard
    Rotus, Victor
    Rous, Peyton
    Rowland, John
    Rubenstein, Douglas
    Ruder, Phillip
    Rukas, Nicole
    Rukeyser, Louis
    Russel, Ingrid
    Russell, Donald
    Russell, Kristina
    Russell, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas of 85 Bloomfiled Ave., now Russell House
    Rust
    Rutledge, Tiffany
    Rutman, Paul
    Ryerson, Ali
    Ryerson, Paul
    Said, Nicole
    Sajko, Halena
    Salinger, Pierre
    Salsbury, Charles/with A.C. Fuller
    Samolin, William
    Sampliner
    Sampliner, Richard
    Sampson, Rachel
    Saint James, Susan
    Sanders, Marlene
    Sanderson, Winthrop
    Sands, Bill
    Sandstorm
    Sandstrom, Harald
    Sandstrom, Harald with David Gugy from student government, and Hassan Abdul Rahman of the PLO
    Sandstrom, Harald with Roger Buckley, Jackie McLean and Derek Walcott
    Sandstrom, Harold
    Sanonicola, Anthony
    Santonicola, Anthony
    Santos, Hubert
    Saschse, Leopold
    Sauliner, Gerard
    Saulnier, Gerard
    Saunders, Robert
    Savin, Peter
    Savitt, Bill
    Savoia, Salvatore
  - Sc-Se (Box Sc-Se)
    Scannell, Daniel
    Scarselli, bruno
    Schaar, Stuart
    Schack, Paul and Merle Abbot
    Schaffer, Lewis
    Schaffer, Marilyn
    Schaffer, Robert
    Schar, Stuart
    Schaus, Nicholas
    Scherer, Mrs. Henry
    Schindelman, Blanche
    Schiro, Mrs. Bernard
    Schmidt, H. P.
    Schoen, Herb
    Schoen, Herbert
    Schoff, Norma
    Schorr
    Schramm, Carl
    Schuller, Gunther with Hartt Concert Jazz Band
    Schulman, Craig
    Schulze, Mary
    Schwager, Myron
    Schwartz, Norman
    Schwinn, Walter
    Scory, Raymond
    Scotsmen: Paul Czellecz, Alan White, Francis X. Reilly III
    Scott, A. Hayden
    Scott, Douglas
    Scott-martin, Laurie
    Scull, Erla
    Scriber, Willam and Jana Van Wie
    Scully, Vincent
    Seabury, Marcia
    Seamon, Alice
    Secor, Jane
    Sede, kevin
    Sedgwick, Ruth
    Seeber, Leonard
    Seidman, Lou
    Selembini
    Selembini, Mr.
    Serbin, Madelyn Robb
    Setzer, Philip
    Seymour, Dale
  - Sh-Smith (Box Sh-Smith)
    Shaffer, Anne
    Shakir, Parveen
    Shankar, Ravi
    Shannon, Edgar F. Jr.
    Shannon, Irwin
    Shapiro, Eli
    Shapiro, Joan
    Sharp, Maurice
    Sharpless, Thomas
    Shaw, Howard
    Sheehan, William
    Sheffield, Carolyn
    Sherman, Merrill
    Shertudke, Hemchandra
    Shetty, Devdas
    Shimkas, Elaine
    Shirer, William
    Shively, Harold
    Shively, Harold, see oversize
    Shramm, carl
    Shuman, William
    Sidedoor Johnnies
    Sidel, Victor
    Siegel, Patricia
    Sigma Tau Delta
    Silber, John
    Silberman, Samuel
    Silver, Harold
    Silverman, Harvey
    Simon, Tobin
    Simons, Harriet
    Simmonds, Diana and OOC staff
    Simpson, Tracy
    Singamsetti, Rao
    Singer, Carole
    Singh, Ram
    Skinner, Robert W. IV
    Slack, Karen
    Sloane, Kathleen
    Slobodkina, Esphyr
    Smidt, Clark aka Smith, Clark
    Smith, Alice
    Smith, Carl
    Smith, Christopher
    Smith, David Rae
    Smith, Everitt Jr.
    Smith, Francis L.
    Smith, J. Joseph
    Smith, Katie
    Smith, Larry Alan
    Smith, Larry Alan wit Moshe Paranov
    Smith, Larry Allen and Faith Middleton at West Farms Mall, 1991
    Smith, Leo
    Smith, Leo T.
    Smith, Milton
    Smith, Olcott
    Smith, Richard E.
    Smith, Robert E.
    Smith, Robert H., Jr.
    Smith, Rosalie
    Smith, Stuart
    Smith, Thomas
    Smith, William
  - Smo-Sz (Box Smo-Sz)
    Smolen, John
    Snider, Todd
    Soderburg, Charlotte
    Sokolon, June
    Sons of Freedom
    Spaulding, Susan
    Spaunburg, Harvey
    Spear, Leroy
    Spear, Roy
    Specials, The
    Spencer, A.
    Spock, Benjamin
    St. Etienne
    Stacy, Paul
    Stang, Robert
    Stanger, Robert
    Stapleton, Richard
    Starnes-Zuniga, Mer
    Starr, Irving
    Steen, K.
    Steena, Mitch
    Stees, Barrick
    Steichen, Edward
    Stein, Edwin
    Steiner, Jane
    Steinam, Gloria
    Steinberg, Margery
    Steinburg, Marge
    Stella, Jim
    Stem
    Stern, Carl
    Stern, Isaac
    Stevens, Malcolm
    Stevensen, Edward
    Stevensen, Edward Jr.
    Stevenson, Catherine Barnes
    Stever, H. Guyford
    Stillerman, ?
    Stillson, Jeff
    Stockton, Edward
    Stolberg, Irving
    Stone, Lyndes
    Stone, Walter
    Stork, Diana
    Streitfeld, Barbara
    Streitfeld, Julian
    Stroh, Bob
    Strong, Sharon
    Styron, William
    Suisman, Michael
    Sukman, Vangrard
    Sukosky, Donald
    Sullivan, Ed and Museum of American Political Life
    Sullivan, James
    Sullivan, John
    Sullivan, Sonia
    Sullivan-Irwin, Mike
    Sunta, Donald
    Superior, Roy
    Supernova
    Sutton, Patricia
    Swain, Elizabeth see also College of Arts and Sciences
    Sweeney, Eugene
    Szelazek, Krystyna
  - T (Box T)
    Tal, Josef
    Taranto (Hamerman)?
    Taylor, Vivian
    Tedeser,Sandy
    Tempelaar, Adrianus
    Temsky, Morton
    Tenney, H. Martin
    Tennyson, Christopher
    Tenret, Jacqueline
    Terry, Benjamin
    Terry, Linda
    Terry, Sue
    Teso, William
    Texas
    That Jazz Band
    Thistle, Matt
    Thomas, DeRoy C.
    Thomas, Norman
    Thomas, Richard
    Thompson, Arthur
    Thomson, Benjamin Calvin
    Tippett, Sir Michael
    Toasters, The
    Tolley, William
    Tomkins, Alan
    Tonkin, Humphrey
    Torrey, James
    Torrisi, C. Richard
    Toth
    Toth, Benjamin and Macbride, david
    Trachtenberg
    Trachtenberg, Francine
    Trachtenberg, Stephen
    Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel
    Trachtenburg, Stephen
    Tracy, Theresa and Scott Petrovits
    Traister, Daniel
    Trampler, Walter
    Traynum-Lindsay, DeLois
    Treger, Charles
    Treger/Watts Duo
    Treidel, Alfred
    Tremaine, Mrs. Burton
    Tuckman, Judi, Gail Tuckman and Caryn Reppen
    Tucker, Lewis
    Tucker, Ralph
    Tumolo, Jacqlyn
    Turetsky, Bertram
    Turner, Charles
    Turner, Mrs. Richard
    Turner, Peter
    Tutu, Naomi
  - Ud-Wi (Box Ud-Wi)
    Udall, Morris
    Unidentified
    United States of Poetry, The
    University Scholars/Lee Chupka, Michael Mongillo, Meredith Hargrove, Michael Ursini, Vivek Nigam, Michelle Lataille, 1990
    Urban, Bela
    Uthoff, Michael
    Vallee, Sylvia
    Valtman, Ed with his cartoons
    Van Atta, Gerald
    Van rynbach, Iris
    Vanesse, Lois
    Vendler, Helen
    Vernon, Kevin
    Vestal, Ina
    Vignone, Connie
    Vincent, George
    Vinson, James
    Viragh, Gabor
    Vitkawskas, Gerald
    Vogel, Frederick
    Voketaiting, Victoria
    Von Dohlen, Robert
    Voth, Ellen Gilson
    Wakeley, Charles
    Walcott, Martha
    Walesa, Lech see Walt's Wall oversize box
    Walker, John
    Walker, Lewis
    Wall, Edward
    Wallace, Mark
    Wallace, Robert
    Wallowitz, William
    Walsh, P. Michael
    Walton, Clarence C.
    Wamiti, Njoki
    Ward, Frederick
    Warner, Elizabeth, see also Elizabeth Warner Paranov
    Warner, Ted
    Warren, Austin
    Warwicke, Dionne (also spelled Warwick)
    Washington, Keith
    Waskowitz, Mrs. David P.
    Wassall, Gregory
    Watson, Stuart
    Weber, Susan
    Weene, J. R.
    Weiker
    Weiker, Lowell
    Weiker, Lowell/portrait
    Weindoter, Heather
    Weinholtz, Donn
    Weinswig, S. Edward
    Weir, Gillian
    Weiss, Ann
    Weitz, A
    Welles, Martin
    Wells, David
    Welna, Cecelia
    Wenograd, Joseph
    West, Traci
    Westheimer, Ruth
    Whealon, Archbishop John
    Wheeler, Gerald
    White, Alex
    White, Foster
    White, George
    White, Marilyn and Phillip Ruder (?) Beatrice Berdinsky, Walter Cogswell
    Whiteride, Richard
    Wickes, Bradley
    Wickman, roger
    Wickman, Roger
    Wiesel, Elie
    Wightman, Gary
    Wilcox, Jeff
    Wilde, Frazar
    Wilde, Wilson
    Willet, William
    Willheim, Imanuel
    Williams, Elliot
    Williams, Ralph A.
    Willis, Robert
    Wilson, Allan
    Wilson, C. Jainsen
    Wilson, Frank S.
    Wilson, James
    Wilson, Mary
    Wilson, Ron
    Wilson, Todd and Anne
    Wincze, Florence
    Winograd, Betty
    Winter Scenes move
    Wion, John
    Wisniewski, Joyce
    Witt, Barbara
  - Wo-Z (Box Wo-Z)
    Wolberg, Richard
    Wolcott, Martha Blake
    Woodrow Wilson Visiting Fellows/scrapbook,1980s
    Woodruff, A M
    Woodruff, Archibald/groups
    Woodruff, Barbara
    Woodruff/inauguration
    Woods, David S.
    Woolf, Emile
    Workman, Harry
    Wortham, Troy "Schoolboy"
    Wright, Douglas B.
    Wright, Mel
    Wyman, David
    Yaffee, Michael
    Yalanis, Despina
    Yale, Charlotte
    Yalow, Rosalyn
    Yankauskas, Betty
    Yanus, Malik
    Yosha, Lee
    Young, Norman
    Zadnik, Thomas
    Zajac, Frances
    Zakarias, Nick
    Zallinger, Rudolph
    Zamuka, Joseph
    Zappa, Frank see Mothers of Invention
    Zenaro, Gwen and children
    Zenaro, Gwen, Matthew and Nicholas
    Zerba, Alexander
    Zerban, Alexander
    Zhu, Jiangue
    Ziegfeld: A Night at the Follies
    Zima, Madelyn
    Zimmerman, Paul
    Zukowsky, Jane
  - Oversize (Box Oversize)
    Groups/Faculty Senate, 1984-1985
    Groups/Faculty Senate, 1985-1986
    Groups/science students and professors, several photos, 1990s?
    Jones, Earle K.
  - Unidentified (Box unidentified 1)
  - Sorting - in progress (Box sorting 1, Box sorting 2, Box sorting 3, Box sorting 4, Box sorting 5)
- Acc. 2013.30 (Box 1.1-3.2, Box 3.3-5.3, Box 6.1-7.3)
  Conditions Governing Access
  The collection is open to all researchers.
  The collection contains reference files on individuals and topic associated with the University of Hartford.
  The collection has been kept in its original order with minor adjustments. The alphabetical order of the files has not been checked.
  Container List
  Box 1.1
  Magnet School 1991-1996
  Magnet School 1997-1999
  Museum of Political Life 2000-01
  Museum of Political Life 1998-1999
  NEASC Self-Study 2001
  Performing Arts Center
  Performing Arts (Thomas Caddae)
  Queen Noor
  Presidential Search (98-99)
  Inauguration 1999
  Box 1.2
  Say Yes to Education 1999-2000
  September 11/Ribbons of Hope
  Upper Albany
  Commencement 99
  Commencement 2001
  Commencement 2003
  Commencement 2000
  Commencement 1998
  Commencement 1987
  Commencement 1989
  Box 1.3
  Heublein Gift
  Magnet School Press Kit 2000
  Magnet School Press 5/4/00
  Magnet School
  Magnet School 2000-2001
  Luce Grant (Seminary)
  Luce Form
  Box 2.1
  President Katsav extra copies
  Israel President Katsav
  History of U of H
  Hawks
  Maniford Out School Trial
  Goldfarb Gift
  Gengras Student Union
  Fund Raising
  Epilepsy
  Entrepreneurial Center (U of H) 97-99
  Enrollment
  Jewish Press
  Box 2.2
  Engineering Application Center
  Educational Main Street
  By-Laws + Incorp of U of H
  Bond Issue
  Bethsaida
  Barney School 2000-01
  Bethsaida Trip (Clips + Releases)
  Barney 2002-2003
  Anniversary (40th)
  Andershonis Reich Award
  Alma Mater
  All University Curriculum
  Aharon Barack
  (Deceased) Schoen, Herbert P.
  AACSB Accreditation
  Hisham Alnajjar
  Ames, Roger (Faculty)
  Anderson, Michael
  Ashens, Robert
  Buckberrough, Sherry (art history)
  Box 2.3
  Barrett, Karen A., 1979-
  Black, Timothy S.
  Blake-Jockson, Joan
  Blanchard, Yvette
  Bolkouac, Edward (faculty)
  Booth, Power
  Bonoca, Jeanne
  Borueinska, Joanna
  Bradley, Tom
  Breda, Karen Lucas
  Breslin, Christine (adjunct photo prof.)
  Breslin, Christine
  Brooker, David
  Brophy, George
  Brown, Stephen
  Dr. Paul G. Bugl, asst, prof. Dept. of Mathematics
  Bullard, Stephan
  Cain, Marcy
  Canedy, III, Dr. Charles R. (Business School)
  Chi-en, Evelyn
  Cohen, Jeffery
  Cohen, Martin S. Dr., (AandS)
  Colarulli, Guy C. (Dr.) AandS Political Science
  Coleman, Susan
  Box 3.1, 3.2, 3.3
  Dr. William H. Coleman, Asst. Prof. Dept. of Biology
  Cosby, Victoria
  Richard Dalphin
  D'Angelo, Robert (Faculty)
  Steve Davis (Faculty- Hartt)
  Day, Victoria Perkins
  Donald T. De Bonee
  Decker, Robert (Faculty)
  Delessert Etienne
  Delventhal, Katherine Ms. (College of Basic Studies- Art History)
  DeMoura Castro, Luiz
  Den Duden, Bernard
  Desmond, Roger (CAT)
  Roger, Desmond
  Desmond, Roger (Faculty)
  Roger Desmond
  DiChiara, Albert
  Dignan, John
  Dix, Douglas (Dr.)
  Doane, Woody
  Duran, Robert
  Eichar, Douglas M. (Faculty)
  Eisenberg, Sheldon M. 1968
  Ellis, Donald- Faculty
  Eppes, Tom
  Esposito, Dr. Bruce J File #3 1976 on
  Esposito, Dr. Bruce J File #1 (old)
  Esposito, Dr. Bruce J File #2
  Erica, George Michael
  Fairfield-Sonn, James
  Farney, Harriet
  Feder, Terry
  Feierabend, John (Hartt Faculty)
  Frey, Mary (Faculty)
  Margret Pfeifer Francis
  Patricia G. Frantz (faculty)
  Fukawa, Hirokazy
  Fuller, Jim
  Gannotti, Mary E.
  Garbalosa, Juan Carlos
  Gates, Allen
  Gauthier, Mary Ann
  Gebo, Sue
  Guiliano, Anthony
  Gluck, Robert
  Godbout, Louis F. Dr., Jr. (College of Engineering)
  Goens, George A.
  Goldstein, Warren
  Arthur Davis Publishing
  Grant, Thomas M.
  Laurence Gould- Faculty
  Gourlie, William R.
  Gray. Jr., Edward T. (Dr.) AandS Chemistry
  Gray, John (Faculty)
  Griswold, Renwick C. (Faculty)
  Gryc, Stephen
  Box 4.1: Ha – J
  Hadad, Allen
  Halus, Siegfried
  Hamilton, Joyce
  Hammond, Caleb
  Hank, Lavin
  Richard Hardin (Faculty)
  Harger, Gary (Hartt Faculty)
  Harney, Jacob
  Harrison, Walter
  Harrison, Walter President
  Haruta, Mako
  Haught, Tricia
  Heinrich, Kathleen
  Hendershott, Anne- Faculty
  Higgins, Rhea
  Holdt, David
  Holzman, Michael (adjunct professor)
  Horn, Michael (Faculty)
  Christopher N. Norton Art School 9/68
  Horvath, Jane (Faculty)
  Housley, Kathleen
  Hudnall, Clayton E. (Dr.)
  Jane Hupfer
  Hurley, John
  Humako-Nurabugau-ary
  Ilumoka- Nwabuzor, Abiodyn (Faculty)
  Drey Elizabeth